jumio.com 2014-04-02

# Privacy Policy - Jumio

## Jumio Inc. Privacy Policy

### 1\. General

This Jumio Inc. Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to the Site located at: www.jumio.com (the “Site”). Jumio Inc. (“Jumio” or “our”) respects the privacy of its users whether they (a) simply view the Site; or (b) use the payment services, payment processing services or related applications that Jumio may make available from time to time on the Site. This Privacy Policy is intended to explain the conditions under which Jumio collects, uses and discloses that information, and your rights in relation to that information. By visiting our Site and/or using the products and services made available to you on the Site, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### 2\. Children

The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13, and Jumio will never knowingly collect Personally-Identifying Information (as defined in Section 3(A) below) from anyone whom it knows to be under the age of 18. We recommend that persons over 13 but under 18 years of age ask their parents for permission before using the Site or sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

### 3\. Gathering, Use and Disclosure of  
Non-Personally-Identifying Information

**_A. Gathering Non-Personally-Identifying Information  
from Users of the Site Generally_**  
“Non – Personally – Identifying Information” is information that, without the aid of additional information, cannot be directly associated with a specific person or entity. “Personally – Identifying Information,” by contrast, is information such as a name or email address that, without more, can be directly associated with a specific person or entity.

_i. Web Browsers_  
Like most Site operators, Jumio may gather from Site users Non-Personally-Identifying Information of the sort that Web browsers, depending on their settings, may make available. That information includes the user’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, operating system and browser type, and the locations of the Web pages the user views right before arriving at, while navigating and immediately after leaving the Site.

_ii. Cookies_  
A “Cookie” is a string of information that a Site stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the Site each time the user submits a query to the site. Jumio uses Cookies to track the pages that users visit during each Site session. USERS WHO DO NOT WISH TO HAVE COOKIES PLACED ON THEIR COMPUTERS SHOULD SET THEIR BROWSERS TO REFUSE COOKIES BEFORE ACCESSING THE SITE, WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE SITE MAY NOT FUNCTION PROPERLY WITHOUT THE AID OF COOKIES. SITE USERS WHO REFUSE WEB COOKIES ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY RESULTING LOSS OF FUNCTIONALITY.

_iii. Web Beacons_  
A “Web Beacon” is an object that is embedded in a web page. It is usually invisible to users but allows website operators to check whether a user has viewed a particular web page. Web Beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides. You may not decline Web Beacons, however, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis. Third parties are not permitted to use Web Beacons on the Site.

**_B. Use of Non-Personally-Identifying Information_**  
Jumio analyzes Non – Personally – Identifying Information gathered from users of the Site to help Jumio better understand how the Site is being used and to help improve users’ experience on the site. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, Jumio is able to better design the Site to improve users’ experiences, both in terms of content and ease of use. Jumio may link Non-Personally Identifying Information gathered using Cookies and Web Beacons with Personally-Identifying Information.  
**_C. Disclosure of Non-Personally-Identifying Information_**  
From time to time, Jumio may also release the Non – Personally – Identifying Information gathered from Site users in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Site.

### 4\. Gathering, Use and Disclosure of Personally-Identifying Information

#### A. Gathering Personally-Identifying Information from Users  
of the Site Generally

As defined above, Personally-Identifying Information is information that can be directly associated with a specific person. Jumio collects a range of Personally-Identifying Information from and about its account holders and Site users. Much of this is information provided by users themselves when they register with the Site, create an account and use the services on the Site.

Site users are under no obligation to provide Jumio with Personally – Identifying Information of any kind, with the caveat that a user’s refusal to do so may prevent the user from using certain Site features. BY REGISTERING WITH THE SITE, YOU CONSENT TO THE USE AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONALLY – IDENTIFYING INFORMATION AS DESCRIBED IN THIS “GATHERING, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY – IDENTIFYING INFORMATION” SECTION.

#### B. Use of Personally-Identifying Information

Jumio may use the Personally-Identifying Information a user submits for any purposes related to Jumio’s business, including, but not limited to providing you with Jumio’s services and personalizing and improving those services for you.

#### C. Disclosure of Personally-Identifying Information

As described in Section 4(A) “Gathering Personally – Identifying Information,” users may, at their option, disclose their own Personally-Identifying Information by any means they choose. Jumio will also disclose Personally-Identifying Information in the following circumstances:

_i. Third Party Service Providers_  
Jumio is a payment facilitator and payment processing provider which offers its services to its account holders and users through the Site. Processing payment transactions requires Jumio to share your personal information with third parties, including but not limited to:

  * Companies with which we have partnered or contracted to provide our account holders and users with a range of essential services including transaction processing, collections, marketing, and managed technology services. Jumio’s contract with these companies require and ensure that these service providers only use your information in connection with the services they perform for Jumio.
  * Banks and other financial institutions that allow us to offer your payment processing services, and partner with us to develop new offerings for you and other Jumio account holders and users.
  * Jumio account holders or users who may accept payments from you by using Jumio’s services.

_ii. On-line Forums and Blogs, and Developer Web Services_  
It may become possible that you may post Personally-Identifying Information on areas of the Site that may be viewed by other users or the public, although we recommend that you not do so. We urge you to use good judgment and not post Personally-Identifying Information that you do not want other users to know.  
YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY LOSS OF PRIVACY OR OTHER HARM RESULTING FROM YOUR VOLUNTARY DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION.

_iii. DMCA Infringement Notifications, Notices of Violations of Site Terms of Use and Other Communications Directed to Jumio_  
By submitting a Digital Millennium Copyright Act Notice (“DMCA Notice”) or other communications about content stored on or transmitted through the Site) you consent to have such communication forwarded to the person or entity who stored or transmitted the content addressed by your communication, in order to attempt to resolve the dispute. For notices regarding violations of the Site’s Terms of Use agreement or other communications (but not DMCA Notices), upon request Jumio will edit out your name and contact information. However, DMCA Notices (including any Personally-Identifiable Information included in the DMCA Notice) will be forwarded as submitted to Jumio without any deletions.

_iv. By Law or to Protect Rights_  
Jumio discloses Personally – Identifying Information, without notice to you, when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Jumio believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Jumio, other users, third parties or the public at large.

_v. Business Transfers; Bankruptcy_  
Jumio reserves the right to transfer all Personally-Identifying Information in its possession to a successor organization or acquirer in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of Jumio’s assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personally – Identifying Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and affirmatively opt-in to accept it. Personally-Identifying Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, will be subject to any new privacy policy adopted by the successor organization.

_vi. Surveys_  
From time to time, Jumio may also ask users to participate in surveys. Jumio will only disclose Non-Personally-Identifying Information collected by means of a survey in the aggregate, unless Jumio notifies users that Jumio will disclose Personally-Identifying Information collected by means of a survey at the time they take the survey in which case Jumio may disclose such Personally-Identifying Information.

_vii. Security_  
Jumio takes extensive precautions to protect the security of users’ information. However, neither people nor security systems are foolproof. Therefore, while we use reasonable efforts to protect your Personally-Identifying Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

viii. Uploading Personal Information to Third Party Sites  
Jumio may enable you to migrate Personally-Identifying Information from Jumio to websites operated by third parties (“Third Party Sites”), including without limitation banking, budgeting or financial services sites. If you choose to use this option, Jumio will disclose your Personally-Identifying Information to those Third Party Sites.

_ix. Marketing Communications._  
If you opt in to receive marketing emails from us, Jumio will email you about products and services that we believe may be of interest to you. If you opt in to receive marketing emails from third parties, Jumio will provide your Personally-Identifying Information to third parties, so that those third parties may directly contact you about additional products and services. If you wish to opt out of receiving marketing emails from us or third parties, please follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

### 5\. Collection and Use of Information by Third Parties

The Site contains links to Third Party Sites and may permit you to post content including Personally-Identifying Information, to Third Party Sites subject to the Third Party Sites’ own privacy policies. Because Third Party Sites are not operated by Jumio, Jumio is not responsible for the content or practices of such Third Party Sites. The availability of links to Third Party Sites on the Site does not represent, warrant or imply that Jumio endorses any Third Party Site or any materials, opinions, goods or services available thereby. These Third Party Sites may ask you for Personally-Identifying Information. Jumio is not responsible for any information these Sites may obtain. Jumio does not oversee their policies or practices in collecting Personally-Identifying Information, and their privacy policies may differ from this Privacy Policy. If you choose to visit Third Party Sites, please review each Third Party Site’s privacy policy to make sure you understand how your Personally-Identifying Information and Non-Personally-Identifying Information may be used and shared with third parties.

### 6\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

Technology and the Internet are rapidly changing. Jumio therefore is likely to make changes to the Site in the future and as a consequence will need to revise this Privacy Policy to reflect those changes. When we revise the Privacy Policy, Jumio will post a notice advising you of the revision on the home page to the Site for 30 consecutive days. For users for whom Jumio maintains an email address, Jumio will email you a copy of the revised Privacy Policy at your most recently provided email address. It is therefore important that you update your email address if it changes. Please review this Privacy Policy periodically for an up-to-date understanding of Jumio’s policies and practices.

### 7\. Compliance with Safe Harbor Requirements

Jumio complies with the US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Jumio has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Jumio’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Jumio commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact Jumio at:

#### Privacy Director

Jumio Inc.  
268 Lambert Avenue  
Palo Alto, California 94306  
Email: [moc.oimujnull@ycavirp](mailto:privacy@jumio.com)

Jumio has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Jumio, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints/ for more information and to file a complaint.

### 8\. Questions

If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please mail or email us at:

#### Jumio Inc.

268 Lambert Avenue  
Palo Alto, CA 94306  
Email: [moc.oimujnull@ycavirp](mailto:privacy@jumio.com)

Last Updated: September 27, 2012
